WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Deep in the South Pacific,
the 20th season of "Survivor"
began with an invasion.
This season,
10 of the greatest heroes
and 10 of the most
ruthless villains
returned for either
revenge or redemption.
The villains took
the early le lead,
led by Boston Rob,
they defeated the
heroes in challenge
after challenge.
The heroes tribe was quickly
whittled down to only five members.
But everything changed when
Russell challenged Boston Rob
for control of the villains.
He joined forces with
Danielle and Parvati
and with some help from Jerri,
they took out Boston
Rob's entire alliance.
Until only Sandra remained,
harboring a grudge
against Russell.
With the merge looming,
J.T. thought he could pull
Russell to the heroes' side
by giving him his
hidden immunity idol.
You don't hand the enemy the idol
gler but when the tribes merged,
Russell gave Parvati J.T.'s
own idol to use against him.
What Russell didn't know
was that Parvati already
had an idol of her own
and at tribal council...
Sandra, that's for you.
?Parvati made one of
the bit moves of the game.
Jerri, that's for you.
She played both idols
to seal J.T.'S fate.
Back at camp, Sandra decided
it was time to strike.
- You want Russell gone?
- Yeah.
Russell's gone.
She did everything in her power
to take out her
longtime enemy Russell.
It's time for revenge
because I've been waiting to
take him down for 30 days.
But the heroes never listened...
Listened... Amanda...And instead
went home one after the other.
Yet, all was not lost for
the two remaining heroes.
Iment Danielle gone tonight.
Because acting like
a true villain,
Russell turned on his own allies.
The tribe has spoken.
With alliances shattered,
no one was safe.
Sandra tracked down a hidden
immunity idol to protect herself.
I would hate to go home
with the idol in my bra.
She played it at the
last tribal council
but she wasn't the one
who needed protection.
Rupert, the tribe has spoken.
Now only five remain.
Colby, in season two, Australia,
he was the sharpshooting Texas
gentleman with a heart of gold.
...
He was a dominant
force in challenges.
This has had a permanent
home here for a while.
He took a worthy competitor
to final tribal council,
...
The winner of "Survivor:
The Australian Outback".
This season he had tougher
time in challenges.
Coach now dragging Colby!
Colby first person out
of this challenge.
Colby, 15 seconds into the challenge,
first person out.
Without immunity, he was
forced to change to a
more social strategy.
When you're staring at a jury of nine,
not having any enemies,
pretty good place to be.
Colby is now the
last remaining hero.
Can good conquer evil?
Parvati.
Parvati has always been known as
"Survivor's" flirty temptress.
When I first saw Parvati
I was like damn!
But she proved herself
a cunning strategist.
I want to play smart this time
and make the right alliances
with people I know I can trust.
And brought her black widow
brigade to the final four
where she ultimately won
the million dollars.
The winner of "Survivor:
Fans versus Favorites."
This season she has
been just as cunning.
...
And just as physical.
Sire and Parvati going at it!
Parvati wins immunity.
Now that she's played
more days than anyone
in "Survivor" history,
will this double threat win
the million dollars again?
Sandra.
In season 7, Pearl Islands,
this feisty mother of two
excelled at sneaky maneuvers.
The two of us, that's it.
She also wouldn't back
down from a fight.
You know what,
I can get loud, too!
Her days are numbered
and I have a mill
that says she won't
be the final one.
The winner...
This season she returned for
the million dollars again
and used the same tactics-
stealth--
he's a stupid ass.
And attitude.
Russell can we just have a minute?
Every time I try to do something
somebody is in my face.
Ever since rul has
eliminated his allies,
she has been working
to eliminate him.
...
I'm against you, Russell.
Will she finally get her revenge?
Jerri.
In season two, Australia,
Jerri became Survivor's
original black widow.
Making a deal with the devil here.
She will ride the team
until it's time to take the knife
out and cut someoneo throat.
She tried to lure people in
with her flirtatious nature.
Pouring hot chocolate
over some hot dude's bod.
But I ain't no hershey bar.
But her pushy attitude
eventually did her in.
No, no, no, we're going
to talk right now.
Jerri, the tribe has spoken.
Are you guys playing cupid?
Yes, you and the dragon slayer.
The black widow and the dragon slayer.
What a combination.
And became's crucial swing vote
to take out major players Rob...
You're smart, Jerri.
Like, you know what to do.
And Danielle.
I'm closer to Parvati
than you think.
Will her new moves give her a
shot at the million dollars.
Russell.
Last season in Samoa,
Russell took over his
tribe by creating chaos.
I think if I can
control how they feel,
I can control how they think.
He made alliances with everyone.
It's just going to be me and you.
I believe you.
- You've got my word.
- You have mine.
Until they no longer
served his needs.
Who's going first?
They're going to be
my little puppets.
When I'm finished with them,
I'll just throw them in the trash.
Burning bridges along the way
eventually cost him
the million dollars.
The winner the "Survivor: Samoa."
This season more of the same.
Getting rid of the machete will
cause conflict in this camp.
Bullying.
You ain't making any sense.
You're not listening to me!
...
And making deals with
everyone in sight.
I want to take you all
to the top three, man.
I want to trust you all the
way to the final three.
Will his aggressive
approach finally pay off?
After 20 seasons,
tonight will be Survivor's
biggest finale yet.
Among the final five,
there are two past winners,
two former finalists,
and between them all,
over 100 tribal councils.
Find out tonight who will
win the million-dollar prize
and the title of sole survivor?
...
Did you it, too!
That's a terrible play because
it shows that she lied.
That's a terrible play.
She was safe today.
How is that a strategic play.
You used an idol to save yourself.
Right, and it was
a bad play for me.
You straight up
lied to me about it.
...
I found out you had an
idol after the fact.
You never came to me and said,
oh, I got an idol!
I played my idol
at tribal council,
and once we came back to
camp Russell was upset,
mad about how we're
supposed to share the idol
and everyone should know.
And I'm looking like,
when you found your first idol,
you used the idol to save Parvati.
We didn't know.
When you got an idol from J.
T., I didn't know.
So how come the minute
Sandra gets an idol I
gotta go tell Russell?
He wants to micromanage the
whole tribe and, unfortunately,
I'm not the kind of person
you can micromanage.
Sorry.
I don't want to talk about it.
It's-- what's done is done.
Let's move on from it.
,, ,
because I don't believe you, Parvati.
I believe you knew about it.
You lied straight to my face.
I did not know about it!
- She didn't know.
- Parvati, you are lying to me.
No, I'm not, Russell!
I didn't know about it.
Neither did Jerri.
Nobody knew about it.
I don't know why it would
even matter if I did.
If you knew about it, it's real sneaky,
that's the problem.
I didn't know about it, okay?
Just leave it at that.
Done and done.
- I didn't know about it.
- She didn't.
- All right, done and done.
- Okay.
Get over yourself for one second.
It's ridiculous.
I just don't like being
accused of being a liar
when I clearlyn was not.
...
I could care less if Russell's
running around stomping his feet
like a little two-year-old
child who got a toy taken
away 240 00:11: 00:11:06,670 because
that's pretty much what he'sacting like
and it makes him a fool.
It's been a thing with me from
the beginning of the whole game.
I've been like get rid of her,
she's dangerous.
We've got to get rid of her.
- We've got to get rid of her.
- She's dangerous.
I'm the last hero standing,
and once again the villains go at it.
And any time this disfunctional
family of villains
is not getting along,
it takes the attention off me
tree mail!
Tree mail? Bag of puzzle pieces.
A puzzle!
A puzzle.
If your steady hands
work to perfection,
but lose control and
it won't matter,
sit back as your creams
and your dishes shatter.
That's the same one
they had in China.
If Colby doesn't win
individual immunity,
he's going to have to go home.
But if Colby does win,
I'm going to have to make a decision.
I know!
The perfect scenario for me to win
is me, Sandra and ger net top
because Sandra didn't
play the game at all
and Jerri didn't
play the game at all.
The jury doesn't
even have a decision.
They almost have to vote for me.
So if Colby wins
individual immunity,
then the best thing to do is
probably get rid of Parvati.
Come on in, guys!
Day 37.
Guys ready to get to
today's immunity challenge?
- Yes.
Parvati, first things first,
I will take it back.
Once again, immunity
is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge,
you will balance ceramic dishes
on the end of a long,
wobbly balancing arm.
The more dishes you stack,
the more difficult it will
be to keep them stable.
When your dishes fall,
you're out of the challenge.
Last person left
standing wins immunity
and a 1 in 4 shot at
the million dollars.
We'll draw for spots.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
Put your arm up on the ball,
everybody.
First plate is the large plate.
Let's get used to it for a second.
This is all about concentration.
Three, two, one.
All right, let's put a
large bowl on there.
Three, two, one.
We're locked in.
All right, let's add
another large plate.
Three, two, one.
The sun is out.
It's early,
and it's already h hot.
You are now stacked
nine dishes high.
Sandra wobbling a little bit.
Jerri starting to
wobble a little bit.
Sandra, first person
out of this challenge.
Take a spot on the bench.
We are down to four.
The next dish you're going
to add is a small plate.
Three, two, one.
Everybody's good.
Jerri wobbling.
Got it back under control.
You have 14 different
dishes stacked right now.
Jerri once again unstable.
Jerri can't hold it any longer.
Jerri is the second person
out of this challenge.
We are now down to three.
Russell, Parvati, Colby.
All right, it's time to
add another soy dish.
This will be the 15th
plate on your stack.
Three, two, one.
Everybody good.
Nice job.
Time to add another dish.
You're going to add a medium bowl.
Here we go.
Wow.
Three, two, one.
Russell with a bit of a waver.
Russell wobbling.
Russell can do nothing but
watch his plates fall.
Russell is out of the challenge.
And we are now down to two.
Parvati and Colby.
For immunity, and a 1 in 4 shot.
Wind coming up.
Big gust of wind.
Hang tight.
Colby starting to wobble a bit,
but getting it back.
Wheaf it takes,
keep running it in your head.
Keep reminding yourself
what you're doing.
Do not drift.
Time to add another dish.
You're going to add a large bowl.
Take your time.
Finding it.
Don't rush. I'll give you
plenty of time to get there.
Colby has his bowl, places it in.
And it's wobbling.
Parvati has hers,
tining to set it in.
Get it level.
Get it how you want it.
Three, two, one.
And we're good.
You now have 17 dishes stacked.
Without warning,
Colby's plates drop.
Parvati wins her second
immunity challenge in a row.
- Good job, guys.
- Yeah.
Parvati, come on ove over.
Congratulations once again.
Parvati safe tonight
at tribal council,
guaranteed a spot
in the final four.
Colby, Sandra, Jerri, Russell,
it has been 37 long days in "
heroes versus villains."
For one of you,
that's as far as you go.
Somebody going home tonight.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
...
Congratulations.
Once again Parvati escapes
her eliminate vote.
I mean, it's unbelievable how
this became works sometimes.
It's not like it's
the end of the world.
We still have one more person
that we can get rid of,
that being Colby.
But, you know, it's still "survivor.
" Anything can happen.
Winning today is a huge deal
for me because I am safe,
and I can keep the rest
of my villains here.
If Colby had won the challenge
twould have been
insanity here today.
And I would have had
had to make a decision I
didn't want to make right now.
Guys, can I just say,
I made my play yesterday
to break you guys up.
It didn't work.
I had my opportunity
today to win immunity.
Damn, you, I couldn't get it done.
Let's enjoy day 37.
I'm proud to be the
last hero standing,
but I'm not going to hustle today.
I'm not going to scramble.
I have enjoyed playing with
you guys. I really have.
I needed to win today's immunity
challenge and I didn't want.
I really needed that one.
So we came back into camp,
I gathered all the villains,
and I gave them my
surrender speech.
- You make me cry.
Oh, come on!
See, that's actually
my last attempt
is the sympathy vote.
If I can't beat you
in the the challenges,
maybe I'll get an "aw,
shucks vote."
Aw, shucks, he's so pathetic,
let's keep him
around one more day.
Pretty good speech, actually.
Hell, I almost convinced
myself I was giving up,
but I don't know how to quit.
It's just not in me.
I've never quit
anything in my life.
So when the time was right,
I made one more attempt.
What are your thoughts?
Send me home?
Yeah.
So the idea is to get rid of me
and hopefully get rid of Parvati
tomorrow and take Sandra in?
That's the idea.
Well, my case is,
get rid of Sandra tonight,
then the three of us have
a better shot at beating
Parvati tomorrow.
Colby comes back from
the immunity challenge
and he's basically quitting.
Then 30 minutes later he
comes up to me telling me,
"hey, man, I think I
still can help you."
Yeah, I think Parvati is
going to get a ton of votes,
especially if she keeps
winning like this.
I haven't had a chance
to talk to Jerri yet.
I got Jerri.
Trust me.
Tonight's tribal council sill
going to be very interesting
because you think about it,
it might be the best
strategic move to keep Colby
and to get rid of Sandra.
You know, I don't trust Sandra
as far as I can throw her.
We keep Colby,
it helps us beat Parvati.
The problem with keeping Colby
is he could possibly
go to the top three.
And that's it. My game's over.
I don't know what to do this time.
I've got to think what is the
best option for me, only me?
I'm going to wait
until tribal council,
see what they have to say,
and make my decision right there.
We'll now bring in the
members of our jury.
Coach, court me,
J.T., Amanda, Candice,
Danielle, and Rupert,
voted out at the
last tribal council.
Colby, the last remaining hero.
Third time you played the game.
It seems like it's
been the toughest.
The toughest out of the three,
but also just the toughest
journey to get here.
The challenges have been the
biggest disappointment, bar none.
I needed this immunity
more than any of them.
Didn't work out.
Parvati's a heck of a competitor,
and if I had won immunity today,
she might be going home tonight.
So, Colby, it would seem
like there are four villains
who could easily say let's
just stay with the plan,
get rid of Colby, and then
figure out what to do tomorrow.
Right.
On the flip side,
if there is a big move to be made,
tonight would be a
great time to do it.
Yeah, there's hope.
And I've been hustling.
Trying to convince Russell
specifically to take
me and not Sandra.
And that's a tough sell.
Would have been easier if
Sandra had won immunity today.
You mean easier to
get rid of Parvati?
Yeah, because nobody wants to sit
next to Parvati in the finals.
I love you to death, Sandra,
but everybody wants
to sit next to you.
That's news to me.
I should be smiling.
I shouldn't have packed, huh?
If it's true.
That's the rub.
You're good.
Say what you gotta say.
So, Sandra, how much of
what you hear around camp
do you believe at this point?
This is "survivor.
" You can't believe nobody.
Parvati, you've been in this game
with three of these
people since game one,
yet the ability to say, "yes,
I believe you, 100%."
No, no way.
I mean, not since day
one and not today.
And listening to Colby say that
it would be much easier for him
if I didn't have this necklace
and I would be going home tonight,
- I'm like, that's news to me.
- I said there's a chance.
I mean, I've been promised
the moon, the stars,
the sun, the sky-- everything.
You know, we'll see what happens.
But I don't believe anyone.
Russell, anybody here
you believe 100%,
there's no chance
they would lie to you?
You just gotta hope that
those true alliances
that you thought you had
and that you tried to
build at the beginning
helped you at the end.
But, you know, sometimes it
just doesn't work out that way.
And, Colby, that inability of
the villains to trust each other
is exactly where your hopealize.
Yeah, and, you know,
so many nights and so many
different days stins we merged--
the villains run through
these implosions, you know,
where the conflict starts.
And that's what you want.
All right, it is time to find
out where the loyalties lie.
Parvati has the necklace.
You cannot vote for her.
Anybody else is fair game.
It's time to vote.
Parvati, you're up.
Colby, today's your
day to go home.
So adios.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
Person voted out will be asked
to leave the tribal
council area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Colby.
Sandra.
One vote Colby, one vote Sandra.
Colby.
Two votes Colby,
one vote sand Sandra.
16th person voted out and the
eighth member of our jury,
Colby. That's three.
That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Colby, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Congratulations on making
it to the final four.
Tomorrow you'll compete in
your final immunity challenge.
I encourage you try to
get a good night's sleep.
You're going to need it.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
I know if wide won
that challenge today,
I'd have a shot at
a million dollars.
It's disappointing,
especially when the challenges are
something I used to be good at.
I guess I'm just an old,
dusty veteran.
My third time in,
I'm just not destined
to win this game.
Finally!
Unbelievable.
I can't believe it.
When Rupert looked like a
crazy killer, yes
I thought he was going to
lunge over and kill someone.
Yeah, he just looked
like a lunatic.
So what?
He wrote my name down.
I don't care.
Just like Colby wrote my name
down two times, too.
Tonight at tribal when Colby
said it would have been
easierto get rid of me
it was kind of an
eye opener for me.
I didn't realize that I
was such a huge threat,
like, with the jury.
Now I feel hike I
really have to try
extra hard to win this immunity,
to make sure that I'm
sitting there in the final three.
She went to the well.
We have to win.
I know.
I need to beat Parvati.
She has really prove tone me
that she is a really
tough competitor.
I've got a nice little birdie.
It's a fairly tough decision now
because my main
alliance is Parvati,
and I'm leaning towards
sending Parvati home.
Guess what I have?
Get out of here!
It better not be a map.
It kind of looks like a map!
I don't know.
Oh, my gosh!
All right, read.
Okay.
"Congratulations, final four."
"You are almost at the end."
Follow the map to the
ceremonial beach.
There you'll find the torches
of your fallen comrades.
At each torch, you will collect
a representative map of
those vote out before you.
At the end of your journey,
you'll offer them up
paying respect to their memory
as they each had a part in
getting you to this point.
"You'll then proceed to your
final immunity challenge."
The rites of passage is where
you pay tribute to
your falleb comrades.
So it's really nice because
this has been the hardest game
I've ever played in my life,
and it's because of the
people they played with.
Everyone fought to play this
game as hard as they could,
so I'm ready to pay my respectes.
They deserve it.
Sugar!
Oh, sugar.
Well, I definitely have more
faith in myself this trip than
last time I played "survivor."
That's the hardest
thing about this game.
You client play with
your heart all the time.
You have to play with your head.
You can't win this game
playing good all the time.
You just can't.
I proved that.
Stephenie!
Stephenie.
She was hard core, too.
I was kind of shocked she
went out second she was such a
tough competitor.
I did get hurt on the first day,
but it's a part of the game.
I can live with it.
I mean, I definitely think
people were gunning for me
because I had such a reputation
for being such a
strong competitor.
My reputation was probably one
of my hardest things
to overco overcome.
Oh, Randy!
Randy, every morning
made me smile and laugh.
He was a good friend to me.
My lack of ability to
communicate with 26-year-old
girls is what got me booted,
ultimately.
And I'm not ashamed of that.
What failzs me is having people
clearly stupider than me
controlling my fate,
and there's nothing
I can do about it.
Cirie.
She was vicious in the challenges.
People underestimate Cirie
as a physical competitor.
She's really tough.
I attempted to play
different this time,
but I felt like I
wasn't given a chance.
I feel like people came in,
you know,
with "we've got to get her.
She's a schemer,"
just straight out.
You don't even know if that was
the game I was going to play
this time.
So never judge a
book by its cover.
Oh, Tom.
He seemed like a first
trustworthy person.
He was the first to go winner,
to go, too, what a shame.
You can be the winner and
dominate one season and be the
casted aside to be dropped by a
guy jumping around on one foot
in your next season I think is
what makes the game special and
what made it worth playing.
Tyson!
He had such a sense of humor.
The funny guy.
When you play with
these all-stars,
everybody is just out
for blood immediately.
I was in control until
I made a stupid move.
I was basically a victim
of my own stupidity.
America thinks I'm an idiot,
but as far as I'm concerned,
I'm still the winner.
Careful.
James!
Seriously what,
a competitor, though.
He hurt his knee and
he still competed
in the next two challenges.
When the big guys fall,
they fall hard.
This time I tried to be a
little more conversational
with people.
I talked more.
I was more friendly, I guess.
There was this injury,
and something you
have to deal with.
I had a great time,
but an injury got me again.
Rob.
Boston Rob.
Rob, if you ain't with me,
you against me.
Too bad-- too bad the poor
old guy didn't be who
he was missing with.
Leave him alone!
He did do a lot for
morale in the beginning.
He told me one time, he said,
"me and you, we're going to get"
along because puerto ricans and
"italians are loud and ignorant"
and I died laughing.
When I first played this game
I was 25 years old.
I'm 33 now,
and I can still hang in
there with the union guys.
I can still do it, but, you know
asht one point I passed out,
but I came through all right.
You know, the new generation of
players are smarter now.
I got to applaud them
for getting rid of me.
It's the first smart thing
they've done in 20 seasons.
They're starting to learn.
Careful.
Oh, coach!
Oh, no.
It's coach.
Benji.
Couch potato.
You guys.
Jerri's boyfriend.
He was my partner in crime
there for a little while and
we had some really good talks.
I can pay homage to you, coach.
Namaste.
I know among all of the
survivors that people have
hated to hate, loved to hate,
and hated to love, I was, and am
number one on the hit list.
And I'm proud of that fact.
Inspiring other people but at
the same time making
myself a better man
and through all of that
myriad of experiences,
I found redemption.
Courtney.
Courtney!
Oh, little one!
I miss you, Courtney!
Usually, on a regular season
you get a bunch of duds.
This time there were
just no pawns here.
It was everyone was the
master of the chess board,
and they were all playing
a different game.
So I sum up the experience as
I'm really glad I came and did it.
I did the best I could,
and, you know,
getting on the jury
on an all-stars,
that's not that easy.
Oh, J.T.
You know what?
You never would have
known that a hero
helped a villain make their
biggest move of the game,
giving him his
hidden immunity idol.
He was the second
winner to go, too.
Poor J.T.
Never give your heart
to a villain, J.T.
I feel like I done really well.
I just, you know, I made a
big move early in the game.
I gave my idol to the biggest
villain in the game, Russell,
and he used it to vote me out.
It was beautiful.
So I would say my experience
this time was much more humbli
Amanda.
That was the first time that
girl has ever been voted out
of the game of "survivor."
Overall, I'm proud
of how I played.
I think my biggest mistake in
this game was giving
Danielle back the clue.
I should have kept it.
That was my lived line.
My congress got the best of me.
I am just not destined
to win this game.
Candice!
Oh, Candice.
I'm glad you got to enjoy
those peanut butter and jelly
sandwiches before you went?
Hell no.
Making it to the 13th
person voted out this time I
think is a much more serious
accomplishment than it was last
time because I beat people that
were hard tore beat this time.
I'm definitely take
a few lessons home.
Danielle.
She was my little Boston brawler.
She always stood up for me.
I miss you, Danielle.
And I'm sorry, Danielle.
I am.
This was the most intense
thing I've ever had to
go through in my life.
And I have no regrets.
I was proud of the way I
performed in my challenges.
And I think I showed that,
you know,
that I have a heart,
and I am a good person,
and I'm not a villain.
Rupert!
He's nice.
We hope your toe gets better.
To have my torch put out
instead of making it to day 39
and being able to sit in
the final tribal council
felt very bad.
But I feel very, very good about
the way that I played the game
and the way they showed
that label of hero,
I deserved it.
Colby, my favorite cowboy!
Colby.
My "outback" comrade.
I think he was the real,
true hero of them all.
Yeah.
I'm almost 10 years older
than I was the first
time I played this game.
Not as fast, not as strong.
Yeah, I'm disappointed.
I'm frustrated in the fact that
I'm out of the game and
the game is still going.
But I'm proud of the way I played.
I outlasted all the other hero
cool!
Okay, light her up.
You go, girl.
Now, that's a fire.
For life.
Come on in, guys!
Are you ready to get to your
final immunity challenge?
Yes!
Parvati,
give it up one more time.
Okay.
For the last time,
immunity is back up for grabs.
Today you will compete
in a "survivor" maze.
You'll each be blindfolded.
To help you navigate your way,
there will be a
series of guide posts
but because you
will be blindfolded
you will have to use your
fingers to read the symbols.
Each guide post leads you
to four different stations
where you must collect a
corresponding necklace.
Once you have all four necklaces,
make your way to the finish,
the immunity necklace
will be waiting for you.
First person to
finish wins immunity,
is guaranteed a spot at
the final tribal council.
That means you get a
shot at the money,
a chance to plead
your case to the jury.
If you lose,
tribal council tonight
could be the last part
of this game you see.
Guys ready to get to it.
Yes.
All right, let's get
you blindfolded up.
We'll get started.
All right, here we go.
For immunity,
and a guaranteed spot at
the final tribal council.
Survivors ready?
Go!
Somebody else go
over the same one.
The only thing that can help
point you in the right direction
are the guide posts.
The guide posts will point you
to each of the four stations.
£¿
move out of my way!
Russell has his first necklace.
He's heading out.
Jerri has her first necklace,
she's heading out.
Parvati has her first necklace.
Sandra still searching.
Jerri using that guide post.
To point her toward
her next necklace.
Parvati using that guide post.
Sandra, that's me.
Sandra tries to take Parvati's
necklace off her neck.
Geez!
Russell is searching for
the second necklace.
Here's the stupid box.
How many times did
I come over here?
Sandra finally gets
that first necklace.
Russell has his second necklace.
Russell now with two necklaces.
Everybody else with one.
Jerri using the guide
post aga again.
Parvati gets lined
up and takes off.
Parvati has her second necklace.
Jerri now with two necklaces,
along with Parvati and Russell.
Sandra with one.
You need to keep in mind which
symbols have you collected.
When ones do you need?
You know which symbols you have.
They're hanging around your neck.
Parvati banging into
all kinds of dead ends.
It hurt!
Jerri has her third necklace.
Jerri now in the lead
with three necklaces.
Russell and Parvati with two.
Parvati has her third necklace.
Parvati, where are you?
I just heard you scream.
Parvati now with three necklaces.
Jerri with three necklaces.
Get away.
Without using a guide post,
Sandra is using something else.
Parvati's voice.
She knows she just got a necklace.
Oh, a box!
Sandra has her second necklace!
Thank God.
Sandra and Russell now
with two necklaces each.
Jerri and Parvati
with three necklaces.
Russell now doing what Sandra did.
Russell now has his
third necklace.
Russell, Jerri, Parvati,
all looking for one
final necklace.
Sandra with two.
She's got to pick it up.
Parvati at a guide post.
Will it put her any closer?
Russell and Parvati
run into each other.
Both with three necklaces
looking for that fourth
and final necklace.
Oops, sorry.
Jerri looking for
her fourth necklace.
Russell has his fourth necklace.
Parvati has her fourth necklace.
Parvati and Russell both
with four necklaces,
both looking for the finish.
Jerri needs that fourth necklace.
Get off me!
This is where
patience will pay off.
If you go the wrong way,
you will lose this challenge.
Jerri has her fourth
and final necklace.
We now have three people
with their necklaces.
Jerri, Parvati, Russell.
First one to the finish
guaranteed a spot in the
final tribal council.
The center symbol will
lead you to the finish
and the immunity
necklace waiting for you.
Russell on the move.
Parvati on the move again.
Jerri at a guide post.
Parvati at another guide post.
Jerri on the move.
All you have to do is
find that finish pole
and grab the immunity
necklace first.
Russell hit the post!
Oh, man!
Russell wins immunity.
For real!
What a finls,
Russell, Jerri, Parvati,
all three within
inches of the finish.
It didn't get any
closer than that.
That was fun.
Very fun.
No, it wasn't.
It sucked.
It was awful.
Well, I have to say in all
of my time on "survivor"
that is one of the most dramatic
finishes of any challenge,
let alone the final
immunity challenge.
Russell, come on over.
Why did you take it off, man?
That's yours.
If you put it on me,
then it's official.
Fair enough.
Glad to do it.
Russell safe at tonight's
tribal council,
which means you will go
to final tribal council.
You will get a chance to plead
your case for a million dollars.
Also at tribal council tonight,
two of you will go on to
the final tribal council.
One of you will go home.
Going to be an
interesting afternoon.
I look forward to seeing
you at tribal council.
Grab your stuff.
Head back to camp.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yief got to talk to Russell,
make sure I'm still his girl,
you know,
because you never know with
that one what he's going to do.
Russell is thinking
I'm his biggest threat
when it comes to jury votes?
I could be going home.
You know, not having that
necklace around my neck,
I have no protection going
into tribal and that scares me.
Oh, my God.
What a day!
That was unbelievable.
So basically, the fact
that Russell won immunity
means that Parvati is going home.
If I watch her torch get
snuffed and her walk off,
I'm not going to cry about it.
I'm going to be
very happy about it.
♪♪♪
?
You know why everybody wants
to take you to the end?
Because I already won?
- Yeah.
- I don't care. I'll take the $100,000.
Because I knew I wasn't
going to win again.
No matter what, in any circumstances,
I'm keeping Sandra.
I think she might get
Courtney's vote and that's it.
I'm going to use Sandra
for me to win $1 million.
She can't beat me.
?
♪♪♪
All right.
I'll take the $100,000.
You know how I feel.
It just-- it just
makes sense to me.
Russell won immunity,
so essentially I have to
do whatever Russell says
because he's waring the idol.
I'm feeling wonderful because,
regardless, Russell's
keeping me around
because I'll never
get a single vote.
But I don't know about that.
?
♪♪♪
♪♪♪♪
♪♪
?
♪♪♪
I gonna go for a walk.
?
You want her with us?
Yup.
♪♪♪
Let me just say something before
you make that decision, okay?
Uh-huh.
If Sandra is with us,
she instantly gets Amanda,
Candice, and Courtney.
I don't think so.
I'd rather take Jerri.
I mean, I'd rather
put ger oat jury
because I've got her vote.
What if she doesn't vote for you?
What if she votes for Sandra?
Parvati wants me to
get rid of Sandra
because she can't
even beat Sandra.
She surely can't beat me,
so she's trying to find out a
way to possibly get second.
It's a scenario that's been
through my head over and over
all kind of different ways.
Best option for me is to
take gerry and Sandra.
That would be the best
strategic move for me.
Your best strategic move?
Would be gerry and Sandra.
No, because Sandra would win.
It gives me two people--
I could sit there and say,
"please, ask these people
what strategic play they made
in the entire game
besides sunbathing?"
Right now, I'm on the fen fence,
because if I send Jerri home,
I'll get her vote.
Fisend Parvati home, I don't know
if I will get her voight.
But I might.
Tonight's tribal council is
extremely a hard decision.
I suffered way too much in
this game not to win it.
I have to win this thing.
?
Let the chips fall where they may.
We'll now bring in the
Mexico of our jury.
Coach, Courtney, J.T., Amanda,
Candice, Danielle,
Rupert, and Colby,
voted out at the
last tribal council.
So, Jerri, you get back to camp.
You don't have immunity.
So not only do you
have to think about
who you want to vote out.
You have to make sure it's
not you who is voted out.
How much of your time is spent
making sure it's not you?
Well, getting back to camp,
you know,
normally, I just walk off and
go sit by myself on the beach
and think about things
and contemplate everything
that's going on in the game.
But today, I didn't
really leave camp.
I stuck around the whole time.
Sandra, you get back to camp.
You don't have immunity, either.
What do I do?
I go to the person with immunity.
Because they're not going home,
and you want to let
that person know
this is why you should keep me
and these are the votes I might
possibly get one, if that,
so, you know,
who better to go up against
because I don't want
to go home in fourth.
So your play to Russell was
take me because I can't win.
Yeah, and Russell
already knew that.
He tells me all the time.
That you can't win.
Yeah.
Well, kind of, no?
You never know what's
going to happen.
She could easily, possibly win.
This is when the
decision making is,
to me, the most important,
and the hardest.
You know, alliances are
going to get broke tonight.
And the decision making is
who do you want to bring
that you, that you can beat
when it comes down to it?
Who has friends, who doesn't,
who might potentially
give you a vote.
Who definitely won't
You gotta sort it out.
You gotta write it in the sand.
Do the math.
Parvati, after winning two
immunity challenges in a row,
you don't win today.
I feel vulnerable.
I feel very vulnerable,
especially knowing that I have
played a good, strategic game,
and if people are trying
to vote out threats,
then I'll probably be walking
out that path tonight.
Jerri, what case do
you make to Russell?
Why keep you?
Well, Parvati's a huge threat.
You know, that's a scary thing.
So that's kind the case I pushed.
Why is Parvati a huge threat?
Because she's been kicking butt,
and she's got a lot
of friends over there.
And, you know, it's no secret.
Right now, that is a threat.
So, Parvati, Sandra says
take me, I can't win.
Jerri says rid of Parvati,
she can win.
What case do you make to Russell?
I say if he's going to be
loyal to anyone in this game,
if he wants to redeem himself...
As far as villains go-
then take me, you know.
I've been your girl
this whole time.
I've been protecting you.
I've had your back
this whole time.
That's as good as I can get.
You've been protecting me?
How have you been protecting me?
We've been protecting each other
since day one.
You disagree?
I think I've been protecting you.
We've been protecting each other.
I've never gone against him.
Which I could have many times
because we argue a lot, you know.
Russell, Parvati could easily
have said, "you're right,
you've been protecting me.
" She didn't.
She looked you in
the eye and said,
"we've been protecting
each other."
It kind of annoys me.
So, Russell, completely different
experience for you today.
You have the upper hand.
You have the power.
Everybody has came to me today
and told me what
they were thinking,
and every-- everybody
made perfect sense.
You know, everybody's playing
et strategically today.
And all three of them
are smiling right now.
All right, let's get to it.
Russell has the immunity necklace.
You cannot vote for Russell.
He is guaranteed a spot at
the final tribal council.
Parvati, Jerri, Sandra,
one of you is about to be sent home.
It is time to vote.
Parvati, you're up.
Hopefully it's you tonight not me
because I want to win. Sorry.
I have respect for you, Parvati.
You have shown again you
are capable of kicking
some serious butt
and for that reason,
it is not a good idea to sit
next to you in the final three.
Sorry I had to do this.
I trusted you the entire game.
I believe you would
have been loyal to me,
but now my best shot
to win this game
is to get rid of you.
I'll go tally the votes.
Once the votes are read,
the decision is final.
The person voted out
will be asked to leave
the tribal council
area immediately.
I'll read the votes.
First vote, Parvati.
Jerri. One vote Parvati,
one vote Jerri.
Jerri.
Two votes Jerri, one vote Parvati.
One vote left.
17th person voted out and the
ninth and final member ofour jury,
Jerri.
You need to bring me your torch.
I can't wait to hear
this story later.
Jerri, the tribe has spoken.
Bye, guys.
Well, congratulations on going as
far as you can go in this game.
Tomorrow night, the power in
this game shifts to the jury.
All you can do is get
a good night's sleep
because you're going
to need your wits
about you tomorrow as you
attempt to convince them
why you deserve the
title of sole survivor
and the million dollars
that goes along with it.
Grab your torches.
We'll see you tomorrow
for final tribal council.
Crap!
One more night!
I was so sure I had this one.
This is kind of the villain way.
I'm leaning towards
voting for Russell
just because he's
played an amazing game.
He's a little reactionary
and hot headed,
but for the most part,
Russell makes decisions that make sense.
Except tonight.
Final three!
Unbelievable.
It's been quite a ride.
Ta-da!
I'm ready to go home to my house,
my kids, my dog.
Although you're trying
tow focus on the game,
you still tend to go
back and think about
I wonder what my kids are doing?
I wonder what my husband's doing?
If I think about my husband,
he's out in Afghanistan.
Is he okay?
Did he make it through today?
You know, it's not easy.
All right, y'all,
I think I'm going to bed.
What? Really?
You're going it leave us alone?
Yeah, there's no need to
baby sit y'all any more.
He's out there in Afghanistan
fighting for our country
and here I am fighting to be
the sole survivor, you know?
But to me it's worth it.
Yeah, I don't get to talk to him.
Yeah, I don't know how he's doing,
but inside, I know he's okay.
I have that gut feeling.
We're all on our own now.
Yeah. You bet.
Every villain for himself.
So I have to focus on the game
because I came for one reason
and for one reason only,
for another million dollars.
And if that makes our
life easier, then why not?
This is how I hustle.
This is how I make my money.
I come and play "survivor."
That's what I know how to do.
That's what I'm best at,
coming out here,
getting my money, going home.
Simple as that.
All right, let's go get tree mail.
Do it.
Day 39, you know,
I said I would do it,
and here I am.
I've done it again.
Oh, my God!
Look at it! It's amazing!
Sometimes it makes
me want to tear up.
It really does.
You say you can do it
but it's a lot harder
than you really think.
And I've done it, twice, day 39.
I want a piece of that bread
chunked off in my mouth.
No one's here to tell us no.
We're villains.
Tonight, I believe I have a
good shot of winning this.
Last season, I brought two people
because I thought I could beat them.
Because they were
the weak players.
And I didn't.
I'd like to say
congratulations to everybody.
For making it to the
final thr three.
I'm bringing people that
other people don't like.
Parvati has a lot of enemies.
Sandra, she didn't do nothing.
At the end of the day,
the reason she's here is
because she's easy to beat.
I'm going to have
to undo my pants.
Tell me the truth,
if I would have been on the jury,
would you have voted for me?
I told you, I would
have voted for Sandra.
I would have voted for you.
If you put me on the jury,
I still would have vote for you.
That's nice of you
but you wouldn't have vote for me?
I would have voted for Sandra.
I have played the game
of "survivor" 114 days.
I don't know if
that makes me crazy.
Probably.
But I think it also makes me
one of the best players
of "survivor," ever.
Your game was just like mine
but mine was a little stronger.
No, it wasn't.
My game was not like yours at all.
I think you'll hear
about it at tribal.
Say what you've got to say.
We all say what we've got to say.
This is it. Every man
for themselves now.
I'm definitely a little mischievous,
a little devious,
and I have definitely
embraced my villain side
this time around.
And you know what?
I've put my heart and
soul into this game
and I'm here to win,
and that's what I want.
He don't know what it's like
to be up against two chicks.
Bam!
My God!
I'm going to burn his hat.
Oh, my God!
Are you kidding?
Good work, lady.
Russell is obnoxious.
I took his hat,
and I threw it in the fire.
I don't care.
I should burn his sneakers.
You could take his bald-head
to tribal council,
it will be all right.
He'll have his buff on his head.
He has a big,
bald patch on his head he doesn't
want anybody to know about.
I've seen it a whole
bunch of times.
Screw it.
That's payback to me for all
he's done to me in this game.
Have y'all seen my hat?
You haven't seen it? No.
Did you pack it.
I put it right there.
I know I did.
I don't think it's about
the money tonight.
I think it's about the
title of sole survivor.
That's all Russell wants.
And if that's what result wants,
that's what I gotta make
sure Russell does not get.
I don't get my hat,
I ain't leaving here.
Well, year going to have to leave.
There's not a day
that didn't go by
that I was trying to focus on
what's the best way for
me to get rid of Russell.
Okay!
And the worst thing of
all is that those heroes,
each and every one of
them are responsible
for their own self-destruction.
When I was out here,
I had to hustle.
I had to make sure all
my stuff was in order
so that when I went
to tribal council
I made it out in one piece.
I didn't hide behind
no immunity necklace.
I never had safety.
I had to take care of myself.
Look at it go wild.
And yet, here I sit, ifiable three.
I think I deserve it.
I want the title of sole survivor.
The villains burn it down.
We'll now bring in your jury.
Coach, Courtney, J.T., Amanda,
Candice, Danielle,
Rupert, colcolby,
and Jerri, voted out at
the last tribal council.
So, after 39 days,
here's why we stand.
We started with 20 people.
10 heroes, 10 villains.
We are down to three.
Parvati, Russell, Sandra.
Each of you having played a very
different game of "survivor."
Tonight, the jury takes over.
Nine people that you had
a hand either directly
or indirectly in
voting out of this game
now will decide which one
of you wins this game,
gets the title of sole survivor,
and the million dollars
that goes with it.
This is their first
chance to address you.
I hope you're ready for it
because you will be
held accountable.
And anybody who lasts 39 days in
this game will have something
to be accountable for.
Here's how it works-
you'll make your opening statements.
They'll address you, then we vote.
Let's start, Sandra.
Okay.
I mean, we all know
how "survivor" works.
I've been sole surviving since
my alliance was wiped out.
I got to the heroes' camp.
I tried to get rid of Russell
three different times.
I'd have to work my way
around things at camp,
try to make sure to take
all the precautionary
measures to ensure that when I
brought my torch in here lit,
that it left heir lit.
And I did that by myself.
Russell.
You know, everybody thinks that
this game is a game of luck.
Some cases I believe it is.
In my case, I don't believe it is.
I played as hard as I
possibly could play,
and for some reason, you know,
when I come here I feel
like people look at me
like I did something wrong.
You know. I tried to play hard.
That's what I did.
If dianything to offend anybody
in this game, I apologize.
But I played the game.
That's all I can say.
Parvati.
I came in to this game
knowing I was going
to play with 20 of the
best "survivors" ever.
What I didn't realize was
the threat that I was to
everyone in this game.
So immediately, I had to put
a line of defense together,
and that's where Russell came in.
He was the dragon.
And instead of slaying him,
I kept him as my pet.
And he displayed his
loyalty at the end to me,
and only to me.
You know, I think I played
the ultimate social game,
the ultimate strategic game,
and the ultimate physical game.
All right. Jury, in a moment,
you get your first shot
atcracying these guys.
I'm going to give you a
moment to get your thoughts,
and then they are all yours.
All right, jury,
it is now your first chance
to address Parvati,
Russell, Sandra.
You're trying to figure out
who's most deserving
of winning this game.
Colby, I get us started.
Russell, did you really just say
there wasn't any luck involved
in getting you here? Yeah.
I do, I do believe that I
got here without any luck.
I believe I got here
with my strategic play.
Ok I was just double checking,
because are you delusional
if you think you can make
it all the way to the end of
this game without any luck.
Parvati, tonight, for me,
I need to learn a little bit about
strategic plays you
made beyond challenges,
because you were impressive
in the challenges.
But I want to know what
makes you more impressive
than those two.
Right off bat, I was the
target from the first day.
I mean, I'm sitting here against
God's plan, basically.
I mean, everyone over
there wanted me out--
J.T. Wrote it in the note
that he wanted me out
because you all thought I was
running a girls' aliengs.
Yb, so I feel I had to fight
harder and make bolder plays.
Probably the riskiest move I
made wasidate I had two idols
because I talked to Amanda
to see if I could trust her
and Amanda was telling
me save yourself.
They're going to vote you.
I gave one to Jerri to save her
and I gave one to
Sandra to save her
in order to ensure their loyalty
to me for the rest of the game.
Well, good luck, all three of you.
Thank you.
Coach, you're up.
Well, the final three villains.
You've got Parvati the charmer.
And also the manipulator.
You've got Russell the schemer,
but also the liar.
And you've got Sandra,
the coattail rider.
We'll start with you, Russell.
You can be a very little man
in stature and also in word.
In the example that
you've set here
should have been only the
penitent man shall pass.
I think if you came to this tribal
and you said that you
crossed the line,
you think you might be one of the
strongest people in the game.
Sandra, I've always said I liked
taking the strongest to the end,
and, unfortunately, you were
fairly useless in challenges.
I played with strength,
with honor, and with integrity.
And I wish I could be
there in your stead.
Parvati.
I gotta te y you,
that coming into this game,
I was dead wrong about you,
that you were going to be a
weak player in the challenges.
You were a warrior in
challeng challenges.
And I respect that.
The ironic Twist of fate
is the day they
finally trusted you,
was the day that you turned on me.
As a Christian man,
I give you my word that
I came in here tonight
without any preconceived notions
of who I was going to vote for,
and I will be watchi watching,
listening,
will be and I'll be voting
for a million dollars.
I have taken that responsibility
quite seriously for
this game that I love.
Amanda, you're up.
Hi.
Sandra, my question
for you is tell me
how your strategy was better in
the game than Russell and Parvati.
I wish my strategy had been better
because if it had been really good
Russell wouldn't be sitting here
pup don't know how
many nights I spent
trying my hardest how do I
get Russell out of this game.
And what happened is,
every time I went to a hero,
I'm I can't believe they
don't want Russell out
and they're taking
him out one by one,
and every time I try to do
something they run back to Russell.
It was crazy.
So did that strategy work for you?
It didn't work for me.
It just never panned out.
I could never get
heroes on my side.
Okay.
Court nigh. You're up.
Well, hello, villains,
congratulations,
especially my two villainess,
I'm very proud of you both.
Parvati, I know you played,
you know, a good game.
I'm really proud of you,
athletic as hell, great.
And then there's my girl,
sand Sandra.
You're loyal as hell, and I think
that that's often overlooked,
especially in a game like this,
and I want to give
you an opportunity to
defend something that
people view as weakness
when really it's an amazing
strength that you take
and you take all the way
to end of "pearl islands"
and you take ought the
way to the end this time.
It's true. When I pick somebody
I'm going to be loyal to,
I'm loyal to them to the end.
I was loyal to Courtney
from the beginning
and she knows I protected her.
Any time I heard anything
bad about Courtney,
I would go bananas and I was like,
"Courtney,
you ain't going nowhere."
They ain't doing
this to you, nothing.
If I tell you I've got your back.
I've knot your back.
I'm look out for you,
and you're look out for me,
but if we need to split,
that's it.
I love you girl.
Take a seat. Thanks, Jeffrey.
J.T., you're up.
Russell, I guess I ought to
talk to you first, old buddy.
Good strategy is getting
to the end of the game
and winning the game.
Getting to the end of
the game is half of it.
The people you voted out,
do you think you've done well
preserving their vote for
yourself at the end of the game?
I really, seriously, believe that
everybody on the jury is going
to respect my game play,
especially this group of people
that's played the game before
and knows how hard it
is to play the game,
and I might not get
anybody's vote.
But I have to stick to
what's going to get me here,
and then hopefully,
the jury will respect the
way I played the game.
How do you think you done,
Parvati?
Uhm, I think-- I love Sandra.
I think the difference
between our game was that
I was a huge threat from day one.
Sandra, was kind of a sleeper.
Like, she gave 50%,
60% at the challenges.
So post-merge, nobody thought
about voting Sandra off.
I had to work in those challenges
because everyone was
trying to vote me out.
Sandra?
Did you only get 50 or 60%
of the challenges. No, no.
Here's the deal-- when it came
to the challenges I gave 110%
but I'm not a physical person--
I know that. But you know
what I want to tell you, too?
I wish I would have known you
were going to throw that thing
into his bag because if I
could have interpreted that
told you you don't
know what you're doing.
I'm not sour about me
going out of the game.
I made my bed, I'll lay in it.
I'm not out for vergence.
I sit here and everybody looks
at me like I'm the devil.
I'm laying in mine.
What I want to do-- s--
thank you y'all.
Danielle, you're up?
Well, well, well, villains.
Hello!
Hello! Hello!
Congrats to all three of you guys.
Russell, it's clear that
there's been a lack of skill
in your jury management.
That being said, what you
heard from all of these people
thus far, would you change
anything about your game now?
You know, I don't regret
anything that I played.
Because if I don't play like that,
there's no way I'd be here.
If that's what you
want me to say--
I'm not going to sit here and
tell you what you want to hear.
I'm going to tell you what-
the truth.
But after hearing what all
these people have said,
how you-- you're not
going to get any votes.
Nobody respects the way you
played the game, Russell.
I wouldn't change anything,
and I don't regret it.
Okay.
That's too bad.
Thanks, Danielle.
Jerri.
Hi.
I am absolutely 100%
undecided who to vote for,
absolutely 100%.
So I'm going to start
with you, Russell.
Right offer win the
immunity necklace,
the plan was get rid of Parvati
and take me to the end.
So carry on from that moment
and tell me what happened.
You know, right after I
won the immunity necklace,
that was the plan.
And all day I thought about it,
and I thought that it would
be a bad strategic move
by me to take you
because you didn't do anything
to anybody on the jury,
and if you were
sitting next to me,
in my mind, you would have won.
Can I tell you what he told me?
Yeah, I was just going to say,
Parvati, your story,
because we never talked. So --
the reason that he told me that
you were leaving is because
100%, he knew he was
getting your vote.
He wanted you on the jury. 100%.
He knows he's getting
your vote tonight.
And it makes sense. You know
what they say about assuming.
Makes an ass out of
you and me. Exactly.
So, Sandra, I hear you tell everybody
how honest are you with people
and how you-- when you say
you're look out for somebody
you look out for them
but I still got blindsided so
you didn't really do that for me.
It's tough.
I gottaayay it's a tough decision.
But I appreciate the insights.
Thank you.
Candice, you're up.
Congratulations.
Final three for making it here.
Russell, you know,
you have to tell lies in this game,
but you can go too far.
You told dirty lies.
Lies that you didn't need to tell.
And you hurt pplple doing that.
Parvati, you kind of played
this game under Russell's thumb.
The whole time.
Like a spouse in a bad,
abusive relationship.
You know, and you
never got out of it.
I wanted you to get out.
I wanted it so bad for you,
but you never did.
I like you, but I
can't support ththat.
As tough as this game is,
it really comes down to
how you treat people.
That's what I'm basing my vote on.
It's not just what you stand for.
It's what you fall for, too.
Thanks, Candice.
All right, Rupert, you're up.
Rusussell, I want to start wt you.
To be honest in this
game is a very har thing.
To be a manipulative, deceiving,
lying person is very eas.
U u took the e easy way out..
And y you think you should
be prd d of how you got here,
yorere sadly mistaken.
Sasandra, ititting
hereisistening y your answers
m meses me feel en wor
a about myy gam py. Y.
I wis y youou a I
had talked morere
t I h been s syed by
what I consider a d
dgusting human being.
You opened the door up for us,
and we kept slamming
it in your face.
I want to say thank you
for all the heroes,
whether they give you
their vote or not.
You deserve a big thank you.
You're welcome.
Look, don't make me emotional.
Parvati, you're a very,
very strong player.
You might have aligned
yourself with...
Terrible.
I didn't have a choice.
No one else would align with me.
It was day one, and seven people
on my tribe wanted me out.
But I want to say you,
as well as Sandra,
deserve the vote because
you worked to get here.
I went up against you
in those challenges.
You fought to be
sitting right there,
and you deserve to be
in the final three.
Thank you.
Thanks, Rupert.
Jury, great final tribal council.
A lot of information has come out.
I'm going to give you guys a
moment to take all of it in,
sort through your thoughts,
and then we'll come back and
make a million-dollar vote.
All right, jury,
you've heard from Parvati,
Russell, and Sandra.
You've had a chance
to address them.
You should have all the
information you need to decide
who's most deserving of the
title of the sole survivor
and the million dollars
that goes along with it.
Tonight you are
voting for a winner.
For the last time,
it's time to vote.
Jerri, you're up.
This is absolutely insane I'm
walking up here going Parvati,
Sandra, Parvati, Sandra.
I am perplexed.
Sandra, in this game,
the line between hero and villain
was blurred most of the time,
but you worked hard,
you put family first,
and you always stay
true to yourself
and that makes you
a true hero to me.
Hey, girl, I'm voting for you.
I know everything that
you had to go through
dealing with Russell and all.
But you are a great player.
I thought you deserved to be
sitting in the final three.
First bump, girl.
Parvati, I was wrong about you.
You were a warrior,
and that is why you get my vote.
King Arthur's journey
has officially ended.
I'm honored that I get to
write your name down again
and give you $1 million.
Love you.
For the last time,
I'll go get the votes.
Well, I want to say that
we couldn't have asked
for a better group of
people to play in this
20th season of
"Survivor: Heroes versus Villains."
Thank you.
Parvati, Russell, Sandra,
the nine votes inside this urn are
about to make one of
you a millionaire,
but you're going to have to
wait just a little bit longer.
I'll see you back in New York
for the reading of the votes.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.MY-SUBS.com